

I Gede Miarta Yasa

PHP Web Developer

081529963914

miarta.igede@gmail.com

https://igedemiarta.github.io/

O Denpasar, Bali

SUMMARY

Hello, my name is I Gede Miarta Yasa, i have a degree in Information Systems from the University of Technology Yogyakarta.

I have good knowledge, especially web programming. I have experience Web Developer and assistant lecturer in web programming and data structure courses.

I have strong skills in programming, I am familiar with MVC, codeigniter and laravel framework, MQSL DBMS, git and github. and I'm used to working with the timeline.

EXPERIENCE

PHP Web Developer (Freelance)

05/2021 - Present

Speedy Global, Bali

Mintenance Web, Adding features and fixing bugs on speedy.global web

Information Technology Consultant (Freelance)

01/2020 - 12/2020

SOS Childrens Village Indonesia, Yogayakarta

Network maintenance, it consultant and information technology management

Web Developer (Freelance)

07/2019 - 02/2020

Gamalama Indah Hotel

Designing and developing hotel stock applications, with submission automation features using the Reorder Point method

IT Department 05/2019 - 11/2019

SMP Negeri 1 Selemedeg Timur

Designing and developing school library applications. to handle borrowing and recording school book data.

Assistant Lecture Web Programming

01/2018 - 11/2018

University of Technology Yogyakarta

Teach web programming, web technologies, frameworks, databases, etc.

EDUCATION

Information Systems
University of Technology Yogyakarta - 3.33

Network Computer Engineering 2016

Vocational High School 1 Denpasar - 3.55

CERTIFICATES

MikroTik Certified Network Associate (MTCNA)

01/2019 - Present

2020

SKILLS

PHP Intermediate JQuery Intermediate
Codeignither Framework Intermediate CSS & Bootsrap Intermediate
Laravel Framework Beginner Git & Git hub Intermediate

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Bahasa Indonesia Native